<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:eonline="http://www.eonline.com/static/xml/xmlns/">
		<channel>
			<title>Is Jeremy London&#39;s Kidnapping Story Falling Apart? - E! Online</title>
			<link>http://syndication.eonline.com/syndication/feeds/partners/mobile/att/plusmo/news/detail.xml?id=187468</link>
			<category>courthouse, jail, busted, </category>
			<description>Celebrities and more - Get bios, pics, and news on your favorite celebrity from Eonline.com</description>
			<language>en-us</language>
			<ttl>10</ttl>
			<pubDate>Thu, 1 Jul 2010 14:24:00 PDT</pubDate>
			<lastBuildDate>Thu, 1 Jul 2010 14:24:00 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<image>
				<title>E! Online - Is Jeremy London&#39;s Kidnapping Story Falling Apart?</title>
				<width>120</width>
				<height>60</height>
				<link>http://syndication.eonline.com/syndication/feeds/partners/mobile/att/plusmo/news/detail.xml?id=187468</link>
				<url>http://images.eonline.com/static/uberblog/images/feeds_logo.gif</url>
			</image>
			<copyright>&#169; 2010 E! Entertainment Television, Inc. All rights reserved., http://www.eonline.com/about/copyright/index.jsp</copyright>
			
			

			
			<item>
				<title>Is Jeremy London&#39;s Kidnapping Story Falling Apart?</title>
				
					<author><![CDATA[Josh Grossberg]]></author>
					
				
				<link><![CDATA[http://www.eonline.com/uberblog/b187468_jeremy_londons_kidnapping_story_falling.html]]></link>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">b187468</guid>
				<thumbnail>
					http://images.eonline.com/resize/300/300/eol_images/Entire_Site/2010517//300.adams.mugshot.london.lc.061710.jpg
				</thumbnail>
				<eonline:imgcopyright><![CDATA[&#169; 2010  Palm Springs Police Department; Charley Gallay/WireImage]]></eonline:imgcopyright>
				
					<description><![CDATA[


<p>Jeremy London&#39;s alleged kidnapper is talking--and predictably denying the allegations against him. But who&#39;s telling the truth in this high-profile he said-he said drama?</p>
<p>In a jailhouse interview with RadarOnline.com, Brandon Adams said there was never any abduction. Instead he claimed the actor approached him and the two went on a mutual &#34;joyride&#34; at the behest of London who was looking to score some prescription drugs, specifically Xanax and Oxycontin.</p>
<p>&#34;There was no gun. There was never a pipe,&#34; Adams told Radar. &#34;We got drunk and I hooked him up with some Ecstasy and Xanax and we took a joyride and partied for hours.&#34;</p>
<p>Not so fast, according to London&#39;s spokesman, Dominic Friesen, who smacked down the suspect&#39;s story.</p><p>The rep said allegations that the Seventh Heaven star--who was busted for marijuana possession back in 2004 and had a prescription  pill problem--had relapsed were false and described Adams&#39; tale as a sign of desperation.</p>

<p>&#34;Jeremy London has consistently passed all random drug testing administered by the State of California and has successfully maintained his sobriety,&#34; said the rep. &#34;The recent jailhouse statements by Mr. Adams are nothing more than a fabricated and false account of the night in question. He is desperate to avoid a life sentence behind bars and will say anything to avoid the serious charges the D.A. has filed against him.&#34;</p>
<p>Last week, London went public about the June 10 incident in which the 37-year-old actor alleged he was held at gunpoint by two men while changing a flat tire and then driven around for 12 hours while being forced to smoke drugs and hand out alcohol in a gang-infested part of the city.</p>
<p>Adams, 25, related his account of the ordeal that&#39;s landed him in a Palm Springs lockup on $500,000 bail. He was due in court this morning but his attorney asked for a continuance until July 15.</p>
<p>He said he and his uncle were hanging outside a local 7-Eleven hoping to get someone to buy them a beer when London and his wife, Melissa, drove up with a flat tire. He didn&#39;t know London was an actor but noted that he appeared to be &#34;acting really strange. . .pacing and sweating and he looked tweaked out. His wife was acting paranoid too.&#34;</p>
<p>At that moment he said a police cruiser came by, prompting a &#34;skittish&#34; reaction from Jeremy and Melissa; in fact, they studiously avoided the officers by running into the store.</p>

<p>According to Adams, after the cops left, so did the former Party of Five star and his missus. Adams and his uncle then walked to a bus stop when they noticed the pair trying to fix the flat on their rented black Ford Focus near an alley. When Adams offered to help, that&#39;s when he says London asked him about the drugs.</p>
<p>&#34;As soon as we got in the car, Jeremy asked us if we could get him five Xanax and five Oxycontin,&#34; said Adams. &#34;Melissa was asking for Xanax too. I told him I could hook him up but that I wanted a couple of beers. He agreed.&#34;</p>
<p>Melissa asked Jeremy to take her home. Reflecting on the alleged kidnapping later, she said authorities told the family that gunpoint robberies that included forced drug-taking were a pretty common occurrence in the area, remarks which drew a sharp denial from the Palm Springs Police Department.</p>
<p>After dropping her off, Adams said the men drove around the neighborhood, &#34;handing out beers to my friends. . .having a good time&#34; before London became annoyed and demanded he get him some pills.</p>
<p>After procuring them, the duo ended up at the suspect&#39;s home with his wife and six kids.</p>

<p>&#34;I hadn&#39;t been able to get any Xanax or Oxycontins up to that point, but I was finally able to get him three ecstasy and three xanax pills. He took all six pills at once. He was out of his mind high,&#34; recalled Adams.</p>
<p>He also dismissed Melissa&#39;s claim that London escaped with the help of one of Adams&#39; cohorts, saying he dropped him off in his neighborhood where the actor checked into a hotel.</p>
<p>Palm Springs police executed search warrants yesterday on the homes of two unidentified suspects connected to Adams, but no other arrests have been made in the case.</p>
<p>But giving Adams&#39; account some credence has been the reaction of London&#39;s twin, Jason, and his mom Debbie Nelson who have spoken out about their concern for Jeremy. Jason called his purported kidnapping a &#34;cry for help&#34; and urging him to use the moment as an opportunity &#34;get the help he needs.&#34;</p><p>Follow @eonline on Twitter!</p>

<p>________</p>
<p>Since we&#39;re on the subject, check out Hollywood Goes Up In Smoke gallery.&#13;&#10;</p>]]></description>
					
				
				<eonline:created>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 11:05:00 PDT</eonline:created>
				<eonline:updated>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 15:27:18 PDT</eonline:updated>
			</item>
		</channel>
	</rss>